COTYEADES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SUMMARY OF OUALIFICATIONS

Computer Information Technology graduate with experience building software applications and websites. Leader who is experienced in managing a wide variety of tasks in team and independent situations. Robust skill set with experience in multiple industries.

WORK HISTORY

Sales Director / Lead Technician

All About Blinds | January 2022 - present

- Experience in implementing effective sales strategies, analyzing market trends, and identifying new business opportunities.
- Skilled at building and maintaining relationships with key clients, resulting in long-term partnerships and increased sales.
- Trained in measurement and installation of high-end window treatments such as blinds, shades and shutters.
- Skilled at programming motorized smart shades and assisting customers with integrating them into their home IOT network.
- Responsible for building proposals based on client needs, scheduling, and workflow management of the installation and repair team.
- Maintain company vehicles.

Grocery Department Manager / ASM Earth Fare | August 2020 - November 2021

Production Worker Smiling Hara Tempeh | February 2020 - August 2020

Assistant Grocery Department Manager Earth Fare I June 2016 - March 2020

Produce Clerk Food City | August 2012 - June 2016

Metal Fabricator / CNC Machine Operator Industrial Tool Services | August 2010 - August 2012

CONTACT

423-302-8622



coty.eades.dev@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/ in/coty-eades-75389423b/



Blountville, TN

SKILLS SUMMARY

- C#
- Python
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- .NET API
- SQL Database
- GraphQL
- Maui/Xamarin
- Software Development
- UI/UX Design
- Unity
- Team Management/Leadership
- Sales/Customer Service
- Metal Fabrication
- CNC Machine Operation

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Northeast State Technical Community College

A.A.S Degree in Computer Information Technology - Concentration in Computer Programming and Software Design 2021 - 2023

Technical Certification in Entertainment Technology - Live Sound & Concert Lighting/Audio Production 2015 - 2016